上集回顾
<i>Last time on "Good luck Charlie"...</i>
我们要来次全家度假
<i>We're going on</i> <i>a family vacation!</i>
你将会面对面的遇到你人生中的真爱
You will come face to face with the love of your life.
嘿  亲爱的  你猜怎么着
Hey, honey, guess what?
我们其实没结婚
We're not actually married.
你想与我共进午餐吗
Would you like to grab some lunch?
-我还没找到他呢  -我所能告诉你的就是
-I haven't found him yet. -All I can tell you is.
-睁大你的双眼  -睁着呢
-Keep your eyes open. -They're open.
他们开始去看那一群...
They're starting to see that this is a bunch of...
哇
Whoa!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
泰迪
Teddy.
斯宾塞
Spencer?
嗨
Hi.
嘿  你来这里做什么
Hey, what are you doing here?
其实  我来这里是为了看你
Well, actually I came here to see you.
噢不会吧  干嘛来看我
Oh no. Why'd you do that?
因为我一直在想着你
Because I've been thinking about you.
有些事情我想和你说说
And there's something I need to say.
别说了  不可能是你
Just please don't. It can't be you.
-什么不可能是我  -就是那个
-What can't be me? -It!
再明白不过了
How much clearer can I be?
-至少你能听我说完吗  -现在不成
-Will you at least listen to me? -I can't right now.
我现在真的有点忙
I'm really busy busy busy.
好吧  但是  泰迪...
Okay, but, Teddy...
啦啦啦啦...
la la la la la...
一会见  贾斯汀  啦啦啦啦
See you later, Justin. la la la la
一会见  布兰登  啦啦啦啦
See you later, Brandon. la la la la la.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
■
后期： Johnny-Z  追忆似水年华
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第二十五集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E25  Snow Show, Part 2
嗨  亲爱的
Hi, honey.
我提早下班然后给你烧了你最喜欢吃的饭菜
I got off work early and made your favorite dinner.
能娶到你真是太幸运了
I am so lucky to be married to you.
正如我妈常对我爸说的那样
As my mom always says to my dad,
没错  你太幸运了
Yes, you are.
嗨  亲爱的
Hi, honey.
我那漂亮的老婆  今天过得如何啊
How's my beautiful wife today?
等下  这...
Wait, but...
-我以为...  -嗨  亲爱的
-But I thought... -Hi, honey.
噢  你烧了布兰登最喜欢吃的饭菜
Oh, you made Brandon's favorite dinner.
等一下  我是嫁给了你
Wait a minute. Am I married to you.
你还是你啊
Or you or you?
我们三个
Yes.
你无法决定我们中哪个才是你的真爱
You couldn't decide which one of us was the love of your life.
-所以你嫁给了我们仨  -这个世界太疯狂了
-So you married all of us. -But that's crazy.
我来告诉你什么才叫疯狂...
I'll tell you what's crazy...
都十年了  我竟然一点没变
It's 10 years later and I haven't grown at all.
艾薇  我现在在滑雪旅馆  然后我遇到了
Ivy, I'm up here at the ski lodge and-and I met.
一个巫师  她告诉我将遇到我的真爱
This psychic who said I'd meet the love of my life.
然后我就遇见了一个真爱
And so I met the guy
紧接着我又遇见了另一个真爱
but then I met another guy,
最后你肯定猜不到我又遇见谁了
And then you won't believe who showed up.
现在有三个真爱  我急需你的救援
And so that makes three guys and-and I need your help.
噢忘了说了  我是泰迪
Oh sorry. This is Teddy.
到山顶后  能让我先滑吗
When we get to the top, mind if I go first?
你好像滑的有点慢
You're kinda slow.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我看过你滑雪  我也看过我奶奶滑雪
I've seen you board. And I've also seen my grandma board.
你俩好像差不多速度
Kind of the same thing.
-总比你的好  -是吗
-Better than you. -Oh yeah?!
是骡子是马  拉出来溜溜
Care to put your money where your mouth is?
不溜  我没马也没骡子
Nope! Last time I did that, a quarter froze to my lip.
我是说敢打赌吗
I mean do you want to make a bet?
赌一百块  让你输的落花流水
100 bucks says I beat you to the bottom.
好吧  赌就赌
Oh, it is on.
你赢的唯一原因就是
The only reason you won is because
我撞上了一块该死的冰块
I hit a wicked patch of ice.
那你敢不敢再来赌一次
Then I guess you have no problem making it double or nothing.
放马过来吧
Bring it.
嘿  快看查莉得到了什么
Hey, look what Charlie got.
一个查莉迷恋上的小正太送给她的礼物
A present from that little toddler she has a crush on.
-真不错  -至少某些男人知道如何对待女人
-That's nice. -I guess some men know how to treat their women.
-你看见我的行李箱了吗  -看见了
-You seen my luggage? -Yes, I have.
-能告诉我在哪呢吗  -好呀
-Do you want to tell me where it is? -Sure.
在你房间里
It's in your room...
你的新房间里
Your <i>new</i> room.
为什么我要有个新房间
Why do I have a new room?
那个  因为我们还没有正式结婚
Well, because you and I are not legally married.
直到你心甘情愿的
And since it would apparently inconvenience you.
再次娶我为妻  否则你将一直流离失所
To marry me again, you'll be lodging elsewhere.
-噢  别闹了  -没错
-Oh come on! -Mm-hmm.
作为一名单身女性
As a single woman,
如果我的房间里出现陌生男子  会令我不舒服的
I don't feel comfortable having a strange man in my room.
-艾米·邓肯  你可真行啊  -啊啊
-Amy Duncan, you're a piece of work. -Ah ah!
请叫我艾米·布兰克霍普
Amy blankenhooper.
你要用回你的婚前的姓氏
You're going back to your maiden name?
没错  是的
Yes, I am. Mm-hmm.
告诉你吧  其实我一直喜欢布兰克霍普这个姓氏
To tell you the truth, I've always preferred blankenhooper.
是吗  那名字有哪里值得你喜欢
Yeah? What is it you like most about it?
是当人们读它时候的哈哈大笑
That people laugh so hard when they say it.
还是人们不会拼写它时的尴尬
Or just that they can't spell it?
出去  鲍伯
Get out, Bob.
嘿  小泰
Hey, T!
噢  艾薇  真高兴你来了
Oh, Ivy, I'm so glad you made it.
你现在可以把胳膊放下了
You can lower your arms now.
你以为我不想啊
Don't you think I would if I could?
你怎么穿这么多件衣服啊
Why do you have so many layers on?
艾薇我不禁冻
Ivy doesn't do cold.
到底什么紧急情况啊
So what's the big emergency?
那个  我遇见了个巫师
Well, I met this psychic.
噢  你还真是说巫师啊
Oh, so you did say psychic.
我还以为电话的信号不好呢
I thought we were in a bad cell zone.
总之  她说在这次旅行中
Anyway, she said I'd come face to face
我将面对面的遇到我人生中的真爱
with the love of my life on this trip,
目前为止我遇到了布兰登  贾斯汀  还有
And so far I've met Brandon, Justin and...
-斯宾塞  -斯宾塞
-Spencer. -Spencer?
那个脚踏两条船的两面派
The two-timing dog that cheated on you?
-没错  就是他  -不
-Yep, that's the one. -No!
你要找的人肯定不是他
That's not the one.
我是说  其他那两个呢
I mean, so who are these other boys?
噢  在那...那就是其中之一
Oh, there... there's one right now.
他是贾斯汀
<i>That's Justin.</i>
噢  挺可爱的  你对他了解多少
Oh, he's cute! So what do you know about him?
我知道他很可爱
That he's cute.
干吗  我只有一天的时间
Well, I've only had one day.
而我只需要一分钟即可
All I need is one minute.
呦  贾斯汀
Yo, Justin!
泰迪  嗨
Teddy, hi.
嗨  贾斯汀  这是我的好朋友艾薇
Hi, Justin. This is my best friend Ivy.
还好吗  贾斯汀  你是来滑雪的吧
How you doing, Justin. You a skier?
-是啊  -很好
-Yeah, I sure am. -Oh great.
再问你件事
One other thing.
-你是富二代吗  -艾薇
-Does your family have money? -Ivy!
抱歉
Sorry.
其实你的回答我没有听清楚
I actually didn't catch your answer.
因为我还没回答啊
That's 'cause I didn't throw it yet.
-PJ  -我要借点钱
-P.J.! -I need to borrow some money!
你说啥
What did you say?
我要借点钱  住口
I need to borrow some money! Stop that!
-好了  我先说  -好吧
-All right, me first. -Okay.
我打赌输了  我需要两百块
I lost a bet and I need $200.
我需要三百块  你知不知道客房服务是收费的
I need $300. Did you know hotels charge for room service?
当然  地球人都知道
Sure, everyone knows that.
你知不知道我的滑雪技术很垃圾
Did you know I'm a terrible snowboarder?
当然  地球人都知道
Sure, everyone knows that.
-看来我们应该早点沟通  -没错
-We really should have talked earlier. -Yeah.
天啊  咱上哪去弄那五百块钱啊
Man, where are we gonna find $500?
注意了  大家  这是您的最后机会
Attention, guests, this is your last chance.
来登记参加冰上之舞比赛
To sign up for the ice-dancing contest.
获胜奖金五百元
Grand prize $500.
看来挺不错的
That was convenient.
只有一个问题...我们不知道怎么在冰上跳舞
Just one problem... we don't know how to ice dance.
记住  这是业余组比赛
Remember this is an amateur contest.
你不需要知道如何在冰上跳舞
You do not need to know how to ice dance.
你太搞笑了  嗨  鲍伯  没看见你在这呢
You're so funny. Hi, Bob. Didn't see you there.
-你的这位朋友是谁啊  -无意间遇见的
-Who's your friend? -Some guy I met.
啊  他叫什么啊
Ah. What's his name?
那个  反正不叫邓肯  这点很确定
Well, it's not Duncan, that's for sure.
好了  我已经开始魂不守舍了
Yep, been there, done that.
谁不会玩你这小把戏啊
You know two can play at this game.
好啊  帅哥
Hiya, doll.
我不想玩这把戏了
I don't want to play this game.
这么说来你想当个厨师和泳装模特
So you want to be a chef and a swimsuit model.
兴趣好广泛啊
That's a good combination.
咱们怎么知道他不是胡说的
How do we know he's qualified?
你能在脱掉上衣的情况下
Can you cook us something?
-为我们做点什么吃的吗  -艾薇
-With your shirt off? -Ivy!
她开玩笑呢
She's just kidding.
除非你真想这样
Unless you want to.
嗨  妈咪
Hi, mommy.
我在大厅和俩女孩在一起
I'm in the lobby with some girls.
没有  他们没您漂亮
No, they're not prettier than you.
好了  排除两个了
Okay, 0 for 2.
那么如果说既不是布兰登也不是贾斯汀
So if it's not Brandon and it's not Justin,
-也就是说  -不会吧  别告诉我是斯宾塞
-Then that means... -No, don't say Spencer!
不可能是斯宾塞  我可不希望是斯宾塞
It cannot be Spencer. I don't want it to be Spencer!
我要说的是
I was gonna say that means
我大老远跑这来  还是一无所获啊
I came all the way up here for nothing,
但是  你说的也没错
But yeah, let's keep it on you.
那就是传说中的冰上之舞  是吧
So that's ice dancing, huh?
看起来够有难度的
It looked hard!
也许咱们应该回大厅
Maybe we should go back to the lobby
看看还有没有五百元的其他比赛
and see if there's another $500 contest.
别这样  我们可以的
Come on, we can do this.
咱们只需按常规那样练练就成了
We just gotta work out a routine.
好了  把你的手像茶壶那样摆好了
Um, okay, put your hands in the teapot position
就像视频中的那样
like they did in the video.
这样吗
Like this?
-有什么好笑的  -没什么  怪痒痒的
-What's so funny? -Nothing. I'm ticklish.
好了  忍耐下
Well, don't be!
-再试遍  -好吧
-Let's try it again. -Okay.
-有完没完  -控制不住
-Stop that! -I can't help it!
盖比  拜托了  如果想办成这件事
Gabe, come on. If we're gonna do this thing,
我们就要心往一处想  劲往一处使
We have to pull together. We have to work harder.
比我们以前要更加的努力
Than we've ever worked in our lives.
我们不仅要把自己推向极限
We have to push ourselves to the absolute limit.
还要超越极限
And beyond.
比赛在四点就要开始了
The contest is at 4:00.
没跟你开玩笑  接下来的一个半小时将会艰苦无比
I won't kid you. It's going to be a rough hour and a half.
风景多美啊
What an awesome view.
完全赞同
I totally agree.
天啊
Oh no.
斯宾塞  你在跟踪我吗
Spencer, are you following me?
那个  可以这么说
Well, kinda, yeah.
嗯  有些事情我一定要和你面对面的说
Um, there's something I really need to tell you face to face.
别  别提面对面
No no, don't say face to face.
-为什么  -听着  这很复杂的
-Why not? -Look, it's complicated.
咱们就不能安静的这么坐着  直到这东西停下
Can we just please sit here quietly until the ride's over?
谈话环节就省了吧
Just no more talking.
这东西停下了
The ski lift stopped.
我说了不要谈话
I hear talking.
一  二  三  四
One and two and three and four.
胳膊胳膊  手手
And arms arms, hands hands.
转圈  二  三  四
And spin, two three four.
亮相
And sell it!
还不错
Not bad.
好吧
Well yeah,
但这个“还不错”能帮我们赢下五百块吗
but is "not bad" gonna win us $500?
你说的没错
You're right.
我们还需要一些特殊动作
We need a special move.
一些能震住评委的动作
A move so good it'll blow the judges away.
我们管它叫“无敌旋风”
A move I call "the cyclone of awesomeness."
什么东西
What's that?
我也不知道  我只是喜欢这个名字
I don't know, I just like the name.
也许我们可以试试在视频中看到的动作
Maybe we could try that move we saw on the video.
你是说男的把那个女孩抛向空中的动作
You mean the one where the guy threw the girl in the air?
我们能说成小家伙和大块头吗
Can we just say the big one and the little one?
好吧  那你的手给我  就像那女孩一样
Fine. Now put your hand on top of mine like the girl did.
说小家伙
Little one!
好吧  现在我要把你扔出去  然后你就转圈
All right. Now I'm gonna throw you and you spin.
在空中时
And while you're up there,
你要尽量的多转几圈
try to do as much twirling as you can.
伸开  注意脸  注意脸颊
Out, face, cheeks,
微笑  再伸  转
Smile, back, spin.
飞吧
And throw!
哇
Whoa!
我可没看见你转了多少圈
I didn't see much twirling.
那是因为你把我扔墙上了
It could be because you threw me into the wall.
再来遍
Try it again.
准备
Ready.
伸开  注意脸  注意脸颊
Out, face, cheeks,
-微笑...-这里又在搞什么幺蛾子啊
-Smile... -What is going on in here?
兄弟情深
Brother stuff.
噢看啊  查莉  这是你的小伙伴
Oh look, Charlie, there's your little friend.
宝贝  当你要甩掉某个男生时
Honey, when you let the guy go,
玩具还是要留下的
you keep the toys!
-邓肯先生  -布兰克霍普小姐
-Mr. Duncan. -Miss blankenhooper.
好啊  又见面了
Well, hello again.
听着  我已是幸福的已婚男士
Listen, you should know that I'm happily married.
其实  不怎么幸福
Well, not happily.
而且也不算是已婚
And not actually married.
快跟雪莉我聊聊怎么回事
Tell Shirley all about it.
这样的  我们发现我们的婚姻不是合法的
Look, we found out that our marriage wasn't legal,
然而我们现在又在吵架
And now we're fighting
因为我不想在度假的时候结婚
because I don't want to get remarried on vacation.
我觉着她太不可理喻了
I think she's being completely unreasonable.
听着  帅哥  爱情就是不可理喻的
Look, doll, nobody ever said love was reasonable.
然而带上一点浪漫的情调  情况会大不相同的
And a little romantic gesture goes a long way.
谢了
Thanks.
这还真是条好建议
That's actually pretty good advice.
如果还不起作用  你知道在哪能找到我
If it doesn't work out, you know where to find me.
好吧  我现在就去试试
Okay. I'm walking away now.
嗯嗯嗯
Mm-mm-mm.
合老娘我的胃口
Mama like!
你看  如今我们被困于此
Look, now that we're stuck up here,
你还是听我说说吧
you have to listen to me.
但  斯宾塞  我们已经谈得够多了
But, Spencer, we've already talked about everything.
我好想你  泰迪
I miss you, Teddy.
我怀念以前
I miss us.
我千里迢迢来到这里  就是为了让你回心转意
I came up here because I want you back.
不成  你不可能是那个“他”
No, you cannot be the one.
哪个“他”
The one what?
是这样的  我撞见了个巫师
Well, I met this psychic.
她说在这次旅行中
And she told me I'd come face to face
我将面对面的遇到我人生中的真爱
with the love of my life on this trip.
然而我接二连三的撞见你
And I keep running into you and...
而且她所预言的别的事都成真了  但
Everything else she predicted came true, but...
我真的很困惑
Just I'm so confused.
没什么困惑的  当我知道你要来这里度假
I'm not. Teddy, when I found out you were coming up here,
有个声音告诉我  我一定要见到你
Something told me I had to see you.
-我不清楚  -我清楚
-I don't know. -I do.
而且你也清楚
And you do too.
我们又继续动了
We're moving again.
是啊  又继续了
Yes, we are.
搞什么笑
Are you kidding me?
撑死我们也就能拿个第二名
We'll be lucky to finish second.
那是因为只有两支队伍
There are only two teams.
那你就配合我
So you're following me.
注意了  大家
Attention, guests,
第一个上场的是夫妻组合
The pairs skating competition will begin with our first team.
PJ和盖布丽埃尔·邓肯
P.J. And Gabrielle Duncan.
是盖比  我是男的
It's Gabe. I'm a dude!
别笑
Stop that!
一  二  三  四
One, two, three, four.
胳膊  胳膊  手  抓住
And arms arms, hands, grab.
来个无敌旋风
We need to do the cyclone of awesomeness.
但是咱从没成功过
But I've never landed it.
现在箭在弦上不得不发
Now would be a good time to start.
伸开  注意脸  注意脸颊
Out, face, cheeks,
微笑
Smile.
干得漂亮
Nailed it.
我们的第一名得主是
<i>And our first place winner's</i>
PJ和盖布丽埃尔·邓肯
<i>P.J. and Gabrielle Duncan.</i>
什么事这么重要
What's so important?
不知道  前台说要见见您
I don't know, front desk says they needed to see you.
如果邓肯家的孩子又捅什么娄子了
If it's anything the Duncan kids did,
那么我就是艾米·布兰克霍普
I'm Amy blankenhooper.
哇
Wow.
我知道这有点突然
Now I know this is going to seem kind of sudden.
但是虽然经过这十九年的做牛做马
After the 19 years and the mortgage and all,
但是  呃  等下
But, um, hang on.
愿意嫁给我吗...第二次
Would you marry me... Again?
这个  鲍伯  我先问你几个问题
Well, Bob, I have some questions first.
你想要几个孩子
How many kids do you want?
-呃...四个  -好的
-Uh... Four. -It's a deal.
嘿  你们听见了吗  她答应了
Hey, did you hear that? We got a yes!
-我能搀着新娘吗  -再好不过了
-May I give the bride away? -I'd be honored.
好的  查莉  你来带路
Okay, Charlie, lead the way.
现在想变卦还来得及
It's not too late to back out.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
And I love you.
耶  恭喜啊
Yay, congratulations!
他们还没结呢
They haven't gotten married yet.
咱能跳过这些环节吗  我想吃蛋糕了
Could we move it along? I just want to get to the cake!
哦天啊  我忘准备蛋糕了
Oh man, I forgot to get a cake.
注意了  大家
<i>Attention, guests,</i>
结婚蛋糕烘焙比赛刚刚结束
<i>The wedding cake baking contest</i> <i>has just concluded.</i>
我爱死这哥们了
I love this guy.
呃  打扰一下  嗨  大家
Uh, excuse me, excuse me. Hi, everyone.
嗨  嗯  我想先敬杯酒
Hi. Um, I'd like to make a toast.
我想对我的老公鲍伯说
To my husband Bob.
虽然我们在一起有快二十年了
Even after almost 20 years.
但每一次我们亲吻对方时  我都会对你重燃爱火
Every time we kiss, I fall in love with you all over again.
这也正是我想说的
And I her.
完了  就这一句
That's it? At's all you got?
-嘿  -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
真是温馨  开始的那部分
That was really sweet. Well, the first part.
是啊  嗯
Yeah, it was. Um...
听着  斯宾塞
Listen, Spencer,
我要...我要和你说些事情
I have... I have to tell you something.
-我真的很喜欢你...-我也喜欢你
-I really like you... -I really like you too.
...呃  但问题是...
...Uh, but the thing is...
哇  真难说出口  嗯
Wow, this is really hard. Um...
我觉着我们还是做朋友比较好
I think maybe we should just be friends.
但是我们在缆车上谈的那些话
But what about all the stuff we talked about on the ski lift.
还有我们的亲吻算什么
And our kiss?
那个  你也听到我妈说的了
Well, you know how my mom said.
每次当她亲我爸时  她又重燃爱火了
That every time she kisses my dad she falls in love again?
是啊
Yeah.
但是  当我们亲吻时  我没有那种感觉
Well, when we kissed, I didn't feel that way.
噢
Oh.
我是说  我以前有  但这次没有了
I mean, I used to, but this time I didn't.
对不起了
I'm sorry.
呃  那现在如何是好
Um, so what now?
做朋友
Friends?
-做朋友  -嘿  女士们
-Friends. -<i>Hey, ladies!</i>
该抛花束了
It's time to throw the bouquet.
啊
Awwww!
嘿  我猜你还没找到真爱  是吧
Hey, so I guess you never saw the love of your life, huh?
没找到  但我想开了  我才十五岁
Nope, but guess what? I'm only 15.
我着什么急
What's the rush?
你怎么就不想想我可是坐了四个小时的车程啊
You couldn't realize that before I took a four-hour bus trip?
我只是很高兴我暂时不用为了找男友而发愁
I'm just glad I don't have to think about boys for a while.
-还不快去要他的电话号码  -这就出动
-Go get his number. -I'm on it.
好了  查莉
Well, Charlie,
我们已经从你的第一次家庭度假中回到家了
we're back home from your first family vacation,
这也是你首次参加婚礼
Where you also went to your first wedding...
没错  老妈和老爸正在重温他们的结婚誓言呢
Yep, mom and dad renewed their vows of love.
快交代  谁是雪莉
Okay, who is Shirley
还有为什么她往咱家打电话  鲍伯
and why is she calling here, Bob?
我在电话簿中找到的
I am in the phone book.
没错  正如你看到的
Yep, as you can see,
所有事情都差不多回到原轨道上了
everything's pretty much back to normal.
我跟你说过多少次
How many times have I told you?!
你要来个勒兹三周跳
You've gotta land the triple lutz.
你杀了我得了
You're killing me!
好了  我退出
That's it, I quit!
你让我上哪去找一个
Where am I supposed to find another partner
小到足够能让我扔出去的搭档
small enough to throw?
祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
我听说这东西有时候会卡住
I hear sometimes these things get stuck.
当我们到山顶后  能让我先滑吗
When we get to the top, mind if I go first?
我看过你的滑雪技术  好像不是很擅长啊
I've seen you ski. You're not very good.
我可以把你像鼻屎一样弹飞
I could flick you off here like a booger.
一个巫师告诉我  我也会在这里遇到真爱
A psychic told me I'd meet the love of my life on this trip.
你是富二代吗
Did your family had money?
我都不知道什么是富二代
I don't even know what money is.